

Upasana Chaulagain

Enthusiastic ICT student with a strong interest in the Information and Communications Technology sector and a background in web development, graphic design, and teaching. With one year of experience as a secondary-level computer teacher, I have honed my communication and instructional skills, which help me effectively collaborate and convey ideas.

EXPERIENCE

Secondary level computer teacher

Emmanuel English Boarding School / Dhulikhel, Kavre / September, 2023 - August, 2024

Software Quality Assurance(Internship)

Axios Softwork / Banepa / July, 2023 - October, 2023

Volunteer Teacher

Gyan Jyoti English Secondary School / Banepa, Kavre / May, 2020 - September, 2020

TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS

Entrepreneurship Development for Entrepreneurship Support Program (ESP)

University Grants Commission / 2023

Young Entrepreneur Soul (YES)

Association of Youth Organization of Nepal (AYON) / 2023

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Communication Technology Education(BICTE)

Tribhuvan University / April, 2021 - Present

Higher Secondary Level (Science)

Sanjiwani Higher Secondary School / Dhulikhel / July, 2018 - August, 2020

CONTACT

upasanachaulagain17@gmail.c om

Banepa, Kavre

https://www.facebook.com/upa sanachaulagain

https://www.linkedin.com/in/up asana-chaulagain-8b6364249/

SKILLS

- web development
- Graphic Designing
- Communication, Collaboration and Problem So;

LANGUAGE

English Nepali Hindi